{
	"questions":
	[
	  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Dog",
		"answer": "Der Hund"
	  },
	  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Dogs",
		"answer": "Die Hund"
	  },
	  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Cat",
		"answer": "Die Katz"
	  },
	  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Cats",
		"answer": "Die Katze"
	  },
	  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Fish (singular)",
		"answer": "Der Fisch"
	  },
	  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Fish (plural)",
		"answer": "Die Fisch"
	  },
	  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Bird",
		"answer": "Der Voggel"
	  },
	  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Birds",
		"answer": "Die Veggel"
	  },
	  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Cow",
		"answer": "Die Kuh"
	  },
	  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Cows",
		"answer": "Die Kieh"
	  },
	  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Pig",
		"answer": "Der Sau"
	  },
	  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Pigs",
		"answer": "Die Sei"
	  },
	  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Mouse",
		"answer": "Die Maus"
	  },
	  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Mice",
		"answer": "Die Meis"
	  },
	  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Horse",
		"answer": "Der Gaul"
	  },
	  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Horses",
		"answer": "Die Geil"
	  },
	  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Wing",
		"answer": "Der Fliggel"
	  },
	  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Wings",
		"answer": "Die Fliggel"
	  },
	  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Animal",
		"answer": "Es Dier"
	  },
	  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Animals",
		"answer": "Die Diere"
	  },
	  {
		  "category": "Pronouns",
		  "question": "First person nominative",
		  "answer": "ich"
	  },
	  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Knight",
		"answer": "Der Ridder"
	  },
	  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Knights",
		"answer": "Die Ridder"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Train",
		"answer": "Die Dreen"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Trains",
		"answer": "Die Dreens"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Teacher",
		"answer": "Der Lehrer"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Teachers",
		"answer": "Die Lehrer"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Author",
		"answer": "Der Schriftsteller"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Authors",
		"answer": "Die Schriftsteller"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Crow",
		"answer": "Die Grabb"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Crows",
		"answer": "Die Grawwe"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Airplane",
		"answer": "Der Aerpleen"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Airplanes",
		"answer": "Die Aerpleen"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "Please",
		"answer": "Bidde"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "Thank you",
		"answer": "Danki"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Sentences",
		"question": "I'm sorry",
		"answer": "Es dutt mer Leed"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "Yes",
		"answer": "Ya"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "No",
		"answer": "Nee"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Car",
		"answer": "Der Kar"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Cars",
		"answer": "Die Kars"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Truck",
		"answer": "Der Truck"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Trucks",
		"answer": "Die Trucks"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Bicycle",
		"answer": "Der Beik"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Bicycles",
		"answer": "Die Beik"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Bus",
		"answer": "Die Buss"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Buses",
		"answer": "Die Busses"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Storyteller",
		"answer": "Der Erzaehler"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Storytellers",
		"answer": "Die Erzaehler"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Boat",
		"answer": "Es Boot"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Boats",
		"answer": "Die Boot"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Ship",
		"answer": "Es Schiff"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Ships",
		"answer": "Die Schiff"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "Christmas",
		"answer": "Grischtdaag"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "Christmases",
		"answer": "Grischtdaage"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Tire",
		"answer": "Der Waagereef"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Tires",
		"answer": "Die Waagereef"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Gasoline",
		"answer": "Es Gaesolien"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Engine",
		"answer": "Die Inscheine"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Engines",
		"answer": "Die Intscheine"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Ticket",
		"answer": "Der Zeddel"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Tickets",
		"answer": "Die Zeddel"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The City",
		"answer": "Die Schtadt"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Cities",
		"answer": "Die Schtedt"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The House",
		"answer": "Es Haus"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Houses",
		"answer": "Die Heiser"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Street",
		"answer": "Die Schtroos"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Streets",
		"answer": "Die Schtroosse"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Road",
		"answer": "Der Faahrweg"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Roads",
		"answer": "Die Faahrwege"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Airport",
		"answer": "Der Aerport"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Airports",
		"answer": "Die Aerports"
	  }
	]
  }
  
